(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-18T21:05:13.624159",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
ひれ伏せ愚民どもっ！
Bow down before me, you foolish mortals!
ころねっ ころねっ ころねっ ころねっ
Korone, Korone, Korone, Korone!
「いいこと？愚民ども 私のことはころ様とお呼びなさい」
"Listen up, mortals! You shall call me Lady Korone!"
いーぬっ いーぬっ いーぬっ いーぬっ
Doggy, doggy, doggy, doggy!
「だから、犬じゃなくて、ころ様とお呼びなさいっ」
"I said, I'm not a dog, call me Lady Korone!"
ころさま ころさま ころさま ころさま
Lady Korone, Lady Korone, Lady Korone...
ひれ伏しなさい 人も妖も全て
Bow down, all mortals and spirits alike!
ひれ伏しなさい 地べた這いつくばれ
Bow down, grovel in the dirt!
ひれ伏しなさい 巫女も幽霊も魔女も
Bow down, shrine maidens, ghosts, and witches!
ひれ伏しなさい 蓬莱の弾幕くらえっ
Bow down and taste Hourai's bullet barrage!
我不死の姫 五つの宝を求む
I, the immortal princess, seek five treasures.
我不死の姫 千年の満月
I, the immortal princess, gaze at the full moon.
我不死の姫 うつつは幻やぶり
I, the immortal princess, shatter this illusion.
我不死の姫 蓬莱の樹海に沈んじゃえっ
I, the immortal princess, drown in Hourai's sea of trees!
ころねー ころねー ころねー ころねーこーねー！
Korone, Korone, Korone, Korone-rone!
ころねっ ころねっ 戌神ころねー！
Korone, Korone, Inugami Korone!
ころねー ころねー いーぬいーぬーっ
Korone, Korone, doggy doggy!
ころねっ ころねっ ころねっ ころねっ
Korone, Korone, Korone, Korone!
「だーかーら…ころじゃなくて、ころ様とお呼びなさいっ」
"I said... not 'Koro', call me 'Lady Korone'!"
ゆーび ゆーび ゆーび ゆーび
Yubi yubi yubi yubi!
「何よゆーびって この愚民共は言葉もマトモに喋れないのかしらっ」
"What do you mean 'yubi'? Can't these mortals speak properly?!"
おかゆっ おかゆっ おかゆっ おかゆっ
Okayu, Okayu, Okayu, Okayu!
「もー、仕方ないわね、ちゃんと聞いてなさい 二番いくよ二番っ」
"Geez, fine. Listen up, here comes the second verse!"
永遠の咽夜も従って遊べっ
Follow and play through the eternal dark night!
永遠の姫 今時の緩さで
Princess of eternity, with modern laxity,
永遠の姫 腰が砕けても踊れ
Princess of eternity, dance even if your back breaks.
永遠の姫 倒れることはない たぶん
Princess of eternity, you won't fall down, probably.
足舐めなさい これで喜ぶの？ 下衆めっ
Lick my feet. Does this make you happy, scum?
足舐めなさい 肌色透き通る
Lick my feet. Translucent skin,
諦めなさい 所詮 愛しき民なのよ
Give up. After all, you're my beloved subjects.
諦めなさい 謎を
Give up on the mystery.
ころねー ころーねー ころねー ころーねーっ！
Korone, Koroo-ne, Korone, Koroo-ne!
ころねー ころーねーっ！
Korone, Koroo-ne!
ころねっ ころねっ 成神ころねーっ！
Korone, Korone, Narukami Korone!
ころねー ころーねー いぬいいぬーっ！
Korone, Koroo-ne, inu-inu!
はーい、というわけで皆様こんばんはー！
Hii, so everyone, good evening!
はい、えーと1曲目は「ひれ伏せ愚民どもっ！」ですね、えー歌わせていただきました。
Yes, uh, the first song was "Hirefuse Gumin-domo!", um, I got to sing it.
ころねスキットと一緒にね。
Together with the Koronesuki.
はい、えー今日のハッシュタグはですね、「犬神ころね」
Yes, um, today's hashtag is "Inugami Korone",
「4周年」……あっ、「4周年」じゃないわ、「4周年」えーとつけて、
"4th Anniversary"... Ah, not "4th Anniversary", "4th Anniversary", um, attach it,
えーよかったらツイートとかね、画像とかスクショとかいっぱい撮って、感想ツイートをしてくれると嬉しいなと思います！
um if you like, tweet, take lots of images and screenshots, and I'd be happy if you could tweet your impressions!
あれれれれ？ どうしたの？
Huh, what's wrong?
なんで泣いてるの？
Why are you crying?
え、殴られたの？
Eh, you got beaten up?
誰に？
By who?
誰に殴られたの？
Who beat you up?
え、どうしたのどうしたの、おいで、おいでほら。
Eh, what's wrong, come here, come here, look.
ころねは優しいよ。ほら隣においで、ほら。
Korone is nice. Look, come next to me, look.
泣かないで、大丈夫だからね。
Don't cry, it's going to be alright.
はい、元気だった？
Yes, were you doing well?
あ、よかったよかった。でも、殴る人なんてね、
Ah, good, good. But someone who beats people up,
もうころねがやっつけてあげるからね！ 分かった？
Korone will beat them up for you! Understood?
はい、じゃあね、このころねスキットが来たということで、
Yes, well then, since this Koronesuki came,
いつものやつやる？ やろっか。
should we do the usual thing? Shall we do it.
じゃあ、おててを拝借。
Well then, lend me your hands.
もうちょっとこっち来れるかな？
Can you come a bit closer here?
はい、おてて見えるかな？
Yes, can you see your hands?
いくよー！
Here we go!
指！指！
Finger! Finger!
あっ！
Ah!
あっ！痛っ！
Ah! Ouch!
あー見て皆さん！
Ah, look everyone!
これが生え、生ゆびゆび……あ、ちょっと気持ち悪い、あ、ちょっと映りが悪いかもしれない。
This is raw, raw yubi-yubi... Ah, a bit gross, ah, maybe the display is bad.
はい、はい、1本じゃ足りない？
Yes, yes, one is not enough?
じゃあもう1回！ 指！指！あっ、すごいよ、あ、痛っ！
Then once more! Finger! Finger! Ah, amazing, ah, ouch!
いてください、取れたての指。
Please look, freshly plucked fingers.
え、大丈夫かな？ え、2本じゃ足りないの？ 3本目も行きたいの？
Eh, is this okay? Eh, two aren't enough? You want a third one too?
いいよ！ せーの、指！指！
Sure! Ready, go, finger! finger!
やばいよ、わっ、どうしちゃった。
This is bad, woah, what happened.
てください皆さん、えっと、今ね、
Please look everyone, um, right now,
ちょっと気持ち悪い、ちょっと気持ち悪いですね、ちょっとこれ、ちょっと見栄えが悪いので、ちょっとスタッフさんに返して、
a bit gross, a bit gross, you know, because the appearance is a bit bad, returning it to the staff member,
ええと、リスナーさんからね、指を生ゆびをもらったということで、次の曲準備していきたいと思います！ちょっとその場で待っててね、ちょっと準備してくるね！
um, having received raw fingers from listeners, I'd like to prepare for the next song! Wait right there for a bit, I'll go prepare!
それは 不思議な まほうの ちから
That is a mysterious magical power.
ぼくと はなすと しあわせになる
When you talk with me, you become happy.
だれでも いいさ みみを かしなよ
Anyone is fine, lend me your ears.
ほっぺ ゆるんで、わらいたくなる
When your cheeks relax, you want to smile.
ハッピー ハッピー ハッピー チルドレン
Happy, happy, happy children!
ハッピー チルドレン、ハッピー チルドレン
Happy children, happy children!
おこりんぼは どこ?
Where's the grumpy one?
ハッピー ハッピー ハッピー チルドレン
Happy, happy, happy children!
ハッピー チルドレン、さみしがりは だれ?
Happy children, who's the lonely one?
それは ふしぎな まほうの ちから
That's the power of mysterious magic!
わたしを みると しあわせになる
When you look at me, you become happy!
ちょっと みててよ じょうずに スキップ
Just watch me skip so skillfully!
きっと いっしょに おどりたくなる
You'll surely want to dance along too!
ハッピー ハッピー ハッピー チルドレン
Happy, happy, happy children!
ハッピー チルドレン、いばりんぼは どこ?
Happy children, where's the bossy one?
ハッピー ハッピー ハッピー チルドレン
Happy, happy, happy children!
ハッピー チルドレン、へそまがりは だれ?
Happy children, who's the stubborn one?
ハッピー ハッピー ハッピー チルドレン
Happy, happy, happy children!
ハッピー チルドレン、ぼくを みてごらん
Happy children, just look at us!
ハッピー ハッピー ハッピー チルドレン
Happy, happy, happy children!
ハッピー チルドレン、けんかは おしまい
Happy children, fighting is over!
ハッピー ハッピー ハッピー チルドレン
Happy, happy, happy children!
ハッピー チルドレン、ぼくを みてごらん
Happy children, just look at us!
ハッピー ハッピー ハッピー チルドレン
Happy, happy, happy children!
ハッピー チルドレン、けんかは おしまい
Happy children, fighting is over!
ファンキー男子 旅立つ時間だ
It's time for the funky boys to set off!
ファンキー姉ちゃん トキメク時間だ
It's time for the funky girls to get excited!
ファキネーション！
Fascination!
ドキメク時間だ
It's time to get thrilled!
諦めやしない 私の未来
I'll never give up on my future!
誰のものでもない
It doesn't belong to anyone else!
もちろん 玉の輿 それも乗りのり
Of course, marrying into wealth is also appealing,
毎日が勝負パンツ
Every day is a battle pair of underwear!
ジャー ジャー ジャージャー…
Ja-ja-ja-ja-ja...
ああ やだー また ちょっと 太った
Oh no, I gained a little weight again!
もう やだー 手柄取り上げないで
Oh no, don't take my achievements away!
もう やだー 制服も脱ぎ散らかして
Oh no, scatter my uniform everywhere!
ダンスでバコーン なんか全部忘れたい！
Dance de Bakoon! I want to forget it all!
ダンスでバコーン 涙が止まらないよ！
Dance de Bakoon! Tears won't stop falling!
こんなにもすごく切ないの どうしてかわかんない
It's so painfully heartbreaking, I don't know why!
今までためたストレスと 今夜でおさらばさ！
Say goodbye to all the accumulated stress tonight!
ファンキー感じ 宴もたけなわだ
The funky vibe party is at its peak!
ファンキー 委員会長 始業の号令だ
The funky committee chair gives the start order!
ファキネーション！
Fascination!
行事のこれだ
This is the event!
輝かしかない うちらの時代
Our era can only shine!
猿にも任せない
We won't leave it even to monkeys!
もちろん バカ女 ウィスキーを呼んで レバレッジ稼いで稼ごう
Of course, foolish girls, order whiskey and build up leverage!
ジャー ジャー ジャージャー…
Ja-ja-ja-ja-ja...
ああ やだー また 調子をこいてる
Oh no, getting carried away again!
もう やだー 人のせい に しないで
Oh no, don't blame it on others!
人のせい に しないでね
Please don't blame it on others!
ダンスでバコーン 今日は全部忘れるよ！
Dance de Bakoon! I'll forget everything today!
ダンスでバコーン なぐさめはいらないわ！
Dance de Bakoon! I don't need any comfort!
心がずいぶん軽くなる
My heart feels so much lighter!
お腹が減ってきたわ
I'm getting hungry!
帰りにおうどん食べて帰ろう 明日が待ってるもん！
Let's stop by for udon on the way home, tomorrow is waiting!
ふー！
Woo!
せーの！ イエーイ！
Ready, set, yay!
ダンスでバコーン！
Dance de Bakoon!
今日は全部忘れるよ！
Today I'll forget everything!
ダンスでバコーン！
Dance de Bakoon!
なぐさめはイラないの！
I don't need any comfort!
心が自分軽くなる
My heart feels lighter,
お腹が減ってきたわ
I'm starting to get hungry,
帰りにうどん食べてくわ
So I'll grab some udon on the way home,
明日が待ってるもん！
Because tomorrow's waiting for me!
ゲラゲラポー ゲラゲラポー
Gera Gera Po, Gera Gera Po,
ゲラゲラポッポ ゲラゲラポー
Gera Gera Poppo, Gera Gera Po!
祭り囃子でゲラゲラポー
Gera Gera Po to the festival music!
太鼓と大拍子 響かせ合ってオープンマイク
Beats and drums echoing together at the open mic,
夜空を踊れ 妖怪ビートの世界を
Dance in the night sky to the world of Yokai beats!
ジャキジャキ華やいだし ややこしいのはなしに
Flashy and gorgeous, leave the complications behind,
ほたえおして イエイ アッソモレイ
Let loose, yeah, assomorei!
餅つきウサギ 月ウサギ
Mochi-pounding rabbit, moon rabbit,
祭り囃子で大ミュージックス
Big music with the festival band!
遠くからもらった飴玉を
The candy I received from afar,
なめずに何度も眺めている
I keep gazing at it again and again without licking.
賑やか過ぎるのお帰り道
On the way back home, it's far too lively,
ほっといてよ
Just leave me be.
今だけひとりで騒いでるわ
I'm just making noise by myself right now.
ゲラゲラポー ゲラゲラポー
Gera Gera Po, Gera Gera Po,
ゲラゲラポッポ ゲラゲラポー
Gera Gera Poppo, Gera Gera Po!
星に振りまくココロは
The heart scattered among the stars,
熱のままに また歌って
Singing once again with passionate warmth,
伝えきれないコトノハ
Words that cannot fully be conveyed,
夜空に咲いた恋花火
Love fireworks blooming in the night sky.
ゲラゲラポー ゲラゲラポー
Gera Gera Po, Gera Gera Po,
歌舞伎者同士 のりおり刻む流行り拍子
Kabuki performers riding the beat, carving out the trendy rhythm,
見上げた夜空に パッと流れ星
A shooting star suddenly appearing in the night sky above.
一人よがりの 賽銭箱とは大違い
Quite unlike a selfish, self-absorbed offering box,
今日のまま夜が更けてくどんどんどん
The night grows deeper just as today is, on and on.
時間は忘れ 街外れ
Forgetting time on the outskirts of town,
だんだん坂の 裏通り
In the back alleys down the sloped street,
言えない想いは つるるまま
Unspeakable feelings remain just as they are,
さよなら笑顔を 写している
Reflecting a smiling farewell.
おべた心は 真ん中に
A shy heart resting right in the middle,
振り向いてよ 月夜に一人 つぶやくわ
Turn around, I murmur alone in the moonlit night.
ゲラゲラポー ゲラゲラポー
Gera Gera Po, Gera Gera Po,
ゲラゲラポッポ ゲラゲラポー
Gera Gera Poppo, Gera Gera Po!
想うほどに 甘くなる
The more I think about it, the sweeter it gets,
真夏の味の 飴玉は
The midsummer-flavored candy,
味わえばすぐ 消えてく
Disappears as soon as you taste it,
花火のように あてやかに
Gracefully, just like fireworks.
Stand up Stand up 立ち上がりよ
Stand up, stand up, rise up!
Stand up Stand up
立ち上がりよ
Rise up!
イナズマチャレンジャー
Lightning Challenger!
立ち上がりーヨ
Stand up, Stand up, rise up!
どん底
どん底！
弱気をパンチング
Weakness is punching!
トンチを利かせてスライディング
Wits and sliding!
泥んこまみれが
Muddy and messy,
勇ましく光るぜ!
brilliantly shine!
貪欲チャレンジ
Greed and challenge!
Don't cry めげずにファイティング
Don't cry, don't give up, fighting!
悔しい気持ちもパワーに変えようぜ!
Turn that feeling of regret into power!
汗かきベソかき夢育ち
Sweaty and dreaming of growth,
根っこはマグママイナス魂
the root is a magma-minus spirit!
傷だらけの雑草魂
A scarred, ragged youth!
見た目オンボロ中身骨太
Looking ragged on the outside,
Stand up Stand up 立ち上がりーヨ
Stand up, Stand up, rise up!
ピンチの谷から初日の出
The first sunrise from the valley of crisis!
Stand up Stand up 立ち上がりーヨ
Stand up, Stand up, rise up!
イナズマファイター
Lightning Fighter!
ドンマイ負けるなスタンディング
Don't mind, don't give up, standing!
行くぜ世界へジャンピング
Go to the world, jumping!
弱気になるなよ 立ち向かえ青春
Don't be timid, face forward, youth!
ど根性 馬力のエンジン
Pure willpower, the engine of muscle power!
Don't Stop くじけず前進
Don't Stop, never give up, charging forward!
相手が強けりゃ強いほど燃えるぜ!
The stronger the opponent, the more I burn!
向かい風のようなシュートが四方八方から攻めてきても最後の砦通がせねーぞ!
Even if a headwind-like shot attacks from all sides, I won't let it through the final fort!
あの娘にいいトコ見せてやれ皆の衆
Show that girl's good side to everyone!
Stand up Stand up 立ち上がりーヨ
Stand up, Stand up, rise up!
曇天吹き飛ばし日本晴れ
Blow away the dark clouds, it's clear skies in Japan!
Stand up Stand up 立ち上がりーヨ
Stand up, Stand up, rise up!
イナズマチャレンジャー
Lightning Challenger!
この日々の努力も
All of these daily efforts,
あの日々の悔しさも
all of these days of regret...
全部×5 燃えろ×3 皆の衆!
all, all, all, all, all, burn, burn, burn, everyone's show!
Stand up Stand up 立ち上がりーヨ
Stand up, Stand up, rise up!
ねじりはちまき気合い100倍
A twisted hachimaki, fighting spirit 100 times over!
勇気のシンボル イナズママーク
The symbol of courage, the lightning mark!
Stand up Stand up 立ち上がりーヨ
Stand up, Stand up, rise up!
掲げよう勝利のフラッグを
Raise the flag of victory!
イナズマファイター
Lightning Fighter!
イナズマヒーロー
Lightning Hero!
デビちゃん！
Devichan!
戌神ころね、来てやったぞー！
Inugami Korone has arrived!
ありがと、デビちゃん！
Thank you, Devichan!
うん。
Yeah.
ねえデビちゃん、
Hey, Devichan,
今日さ、難しいステージじゃん？
today was... quite a thriller, huh?
そう、今日ねこの4周年で迎えたんだよ。
We finished it with a great success today!
うん。
Yeah.
あの、デビちゃんとうね、記念ライブでね歌って踊りたかったから、今日はすごい夢叶っちゃったよ。
Because Devichan and I wanted to sing, dance, and have fun together in a 3D live.
うん、よかったね！
Yeah, that's great!
ま、たまにはこういうのもいいもんじゃんね。また一緒にやってもいいよ。
Well, sometimes this kind of thing is good, too. You can play again anytime!
え、本当に？じゃあさ、またゲームとか一緒にやろう！
Really? Then let's play games together again!
ま、いいよ。
Well, okay.
じゃ、これからも頑張りたまえ、ではない！
Then keep doing your best from now on, too!
ありがと、デビちゃん！またね、気をつけてね！
Thank you, Devichan! See you again, be careful!
あ、帰っていきました、デヴィちゃんが。
Ah, Dev-chan already went home.
デヴィちゃん、ありがとう！
Dev-chan, thank you!
ねえ、ちょっと、次もちょっとゲストを呼んでるんですが、
Say, um, we're going to have another guest for the next part, but...
ちょっと、あの個人的にすごい緊張してて、あの、ものすごい人を、あの、呼んでいまして、
I'm personally super nervous because... um, I've invited someone incredible,
あの、ちょっと、緊張するんで1回、あの、ドキます。緊張します。どうしよう。
so... um, I need a moment to calm my nerves. I'm so nervous, what should I do?
夜空の星が輝く陰で 悪の笑いがこだまする
In the shadow of glittering stars in the night sky, evil laughter echoes.
星から星に泣く人の 涙背負って宇宙の始末
Carrying the tears of people weeping from star to star, we settle the cosmos' scores!
銀河旋風ブライガー お呼びとあらば即参上！
Galactic Whirlwind Braiger! Summon us, and we arrive instantly!
ジェイ・ジェイ・情け無用
J-J-No mercy!
アステロイド・ベルトの
On the asteroid belt,
アウトローも震えだす
even outlaws start to tremble—
コズモレンジャー・ジェイナイン
Cosmo Ranger J9!
宇宙空間突っ走るのさ ブライサンダー ブライサンダー
Rushing through outer space—Brythunder! Brythunder!
十万光年 星のきらめき 飛び交うブライスター
One hundred thousand light-years of starlight, flying Bristar!
広がるプラズマ ウ・ウ・ウルフのマーク アー・アイツは
Spreading plasma, the W-W-Wolf mark! Ah... that guy is...
銀河旋風 銀河旋風
Galactic Whirlwind! Galactic Whirlwind!
ブライガー！
Braiger!
ジェイ・ジェイ・恐れ無用
J-J-Fear no one!
悪の限り暴れる
Rampaging in evil's full extent,
アウトローも逃げてゆく
even outlaws run away—
コズモレンジャー・ジェイナイン
Cosmo Ranger J9!
スーパーポリス自慢のマシン ブライサンダー ブライサンダー
The Super Police's prized machine—Brythunder! Brythunder!
命知らずを乗せてはるかに 飛び立つブライスター
Carrying daredevils far away, taking flight—Bristar!
広がるプラズマ ウ・ウ・ウルフのマーク アー・アイツは 銀河旋風
Spreading plasma, the W-W-Wolf mark! Ah... that guy is... Galactic Whirlwind!
銀河旋風 ブライガー！
Galactic Whirlwind Braiger!
ブライガー！ ブライガー！
Braiger! Braiger!
ブライガー！ はい！ ブライガー！
Braiger! Yes! Braiger!
なんと！平、平竿さんがいらしてくれましたー！
And amazingly... Taira-san came to join us!
コロナさん、4周年おめでとうございます！
Korone-san, congratulations on your 4th anniversary!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
はい、うれしい！ いや、こちらもうれしいです。
I'm so happy! / I'm happy too.
いやもう、今すごい緊張と嬉しさで、色々感情が大変なことになっておりまして、
I'm so super nervous and happy right now, my emotions are all over the place!
絶対みんなも聞いたことある、名曲アニメソングを数々歌っていらっしゃるすごい方なんです。
Everyone has definitely heard them before—he's an incredible singer of numerous iconic anime songs!
ありがとうございます。丁寧なご紹介を。
Thank you very much for the polite introduction.
まさかの、前回の3Dライブで、こーねが歌った復活のイデオンを、なんと平竿さんが聞いてくださって……
And amazingly, at my last 3D live, Taira-san actually listened to my cover of "Fukkatsu no Ideon"...
聞いてくださったっていうか聞いたんですよもう、びっくり
Not just listened, I heard it! I was so surprised,
とっても可愛い声のイデオンが聞こえてきて、とっても嬉しかったです。
and heard this super cute-voiced Ideon, I was so happy.
ありがとうございます。
Thank you very much!
で、今回ね、あの、こーねが、あの平竿さん、よかったらあのライブに出てくれませんかって、あの、お声がけをかけたらですね、あの、なんとなんと、心良く、いいですよと、お引き受けしてくださってですね……！
And this time, when I reached out to ask, "Taira-san, if you're willing, would you perform at my live?", you so graciously agreed...!
（笑）
(Laughs)
本当に本当にありがとうございました！
Thank you truly, truly so much!
いや、こちらこそありがとうございます。こんなね、僕の、あのこの大切な一曲をね、ころねさんとジョイントできるなんて、こんな最高なことないじゃないですか！
To be able to join Korone-san in performing this precious song of mine... there's nothing better than this!
もう喜んできちゃったよ！
I was so thrilled!
今回はね、あの、来ていただいただけじゃなくて、あの銀河旋風ブライガーっていうね、名曲を一緒に歌っていただいて……
And this time, not only did you come, but you sang that masterpiece "Galactic Whirlwind Braiger" with me...
一緒にやってくれてありがとう！歌い方も教えていただいて、ありがとうございます。
Thank you for doing it with me! And thank you for teaching me how to sing it.
いや何にも教えてないよ！もうころね節で十分です。ありがとうございます。
I didn't teach you anything! Your own Korone style is plenty. Thank you!
平竿さんは、あのバーチャル空間初めてだ と思うんですけど、どうですか、ちょっと来てみて。
Taira-san, I think this is your first time in a virtual space—how is it, experiencing it?
うん、もうやっと今少し慣れてきたかな。
Yeah, I'm finally getting a bit used to it now.
な感じしますか？
How does it feel?
いや、変な感じはないよ。
No, it doesn't feel weird at all.
あ、馴染んで、でも馴染んでますもんね。
Ah, but you're blending right in.
もうなんか楽しくコロネさん歌えてるなっていう気持ちだけで馴染んでます。
I'm just happy singing along with Korone, so I'm already blending right in.
大丈夫です。
It's fine.
ありがとうございます。
Thank you very much.
あ、ちなみになんですけど、もう一曲一緒に歌ってもらうことって可能なんでしょうか？
Ah, by the way, would it be possible to sing one more song together?
もちろんですよ。
Of course!
え、本当ですか？
Eh, really?
ありがとうございます。
Thank you!
こちらこそよろしくお願いします。
The pleasure is mine.
ころねの大好きなこの曲ではお願いしたいと思います。
I'd like to ask for this song that Korone loves so much.
僕もこの曲でコロネさんのことよく知りましたので。
I got to know Korone well through this song too.
じゃあみんなも何が来るかわかってると思うけど、タイトル一緒にいいでしょうか？
Everyone probably knows what's coming, but can we announce the title together?
はい、いいですよ。
Sure, sounds good.
はい、行きます。
Okay, here we go.
せーの、復活のイデオン！
Ready, set... Ideon: A Contact!
きこえるか きこえるだろう はるかな轟き
Can you hear it? I'm sure you can hear that distant roar.
はるかな轟き
...the distant roar.
闇の中 魂ゆさぶる 目覚め始まる
In the darkness, it shakes your soul, awakening begins.
大地わり そそり立つ姿 正義の証か
Splitting the earth, standing tall, is this the proof of justice?
伝説の巨人の力 銀河きりさく
The legendary giant's power rips apart the galaxy!
雄叫びが 電光石火の一撃をよぶ
A roar calls forth a lightning-fast strike!
ふるえるな 瞳こらせよ 復活の時
Don't tremble, focus your eyes, the time of resurrection.
人よ 生命よ 始まりを見る
Oh humanity, oh life, witness the beginning!
スペース・ランナウェイ イデオン イデオン
Space Runaway Ideon, Ideon!
たたかうか たたかえるか おびえる魂よ
Will you fight? Can you fight, oh frightened soul?
せまりくる 悪の力に 勇気を示せ
Show your courage against the encroaching forces of evil!
空にとぶ 輝く姿 生命の叫びか
Flying through the sky, a shining figure, is this the cry of life?
伝説の巨人の力 銀河きりさく
The legendary giant's power rips apart the galaxy!
必殺の技が撃つの書は我が身なのかと
Is the finishing blow coming from my own body?
おそるな 魂ひらけよ 復活の時
Do not fear, open your soul, the time of resurrection.
人よ 生命よ 力を見る
Oh humanity, oh life, witness the power!
スペース・ランナウェイ イデオン イデオン
Space Runaway Ideon, Ideon!
やっかね！ありがとう！
We did it! Thank you!
ありがとうございます。
Thank you very much.
あの、この曲は前回も歌ったんですけど、歌った理由としては
Um, we sang this song last time too, but the reason we sang it...
本当に大好きな曲で、入りから優しくころねさんの歌声が聞こえてきたと思ったら力強くどんどんになっていって、それがすごい聞いててすごく気持ちよくて大好きで...
...is because it's a song I really love. Starting off with Korone's gentle singing voice, and then getting more and more powerful, it feels so good to listen to and I love it...
そうそうそう、そこがこの歌の、イデオンのいいところですよ。
Exactly! That's the great thing about Ideon's song.
あの、静かな立ち上がりでね、そっからロックになっていくというね。
Starting out quietly and then turning into rock.
そう、本当にカッコいい曲で。特にね、ころねさん2番の歌詞のね、
Yes, it's a really cool song. Especially Korone's lyrics in the second verse...
今日はころねさんが歌ってくれた「戦うか 戦えるか おびえる心よ」なんて
...that you sang today: "'Will you fight, can you fight, oh frightened heart'..."
グッときますよね！
It really hits you!
はい、グッときました。
Yes, it touched my heart.
今日も隣で一緒に歌っていただいて、本当に2曲ともありがとうございました！
Thank you so much for singing together by my side for both songs today!
ありがとうございました！
Thank you very much!
じゃあそろそろあれですかね、お別れの時間なんでしょうか？
Well, is it almost time to say goodbye?
あ、そう？そうなの？どうなんでしょうかね？
Oh, really? Is that so? I wonder?
じゃあ指指かな？あ、指指で、じゃあ最後はお別れで、本当にありがとうございました！
Then fingers? Ah, with fingers, let's say goodbye at the end. Thank you so much!
こちらこそ、ありがとうございました！
Thank you too!
ありがとうございました！
Thank you very much!
指指！
Yubi yubi!
はい、またよろしくね！じゃあここでも準備があるから、行ってくるね！
Yes, looking forward to next time! Well, preparations are here too, so I'll be going!
はい、これからも頑張ってください！ありがとうございます！
Yes, please keep doing your best! Thank you!
夕暮れの かなたから蜃気楼
A mirage from beyond the twilight,
会いたくて 会いたくて
wanting to see you, wanting to see you,
会えなくて 会えなくて
unable to see you, unable to see you.
あなた ユートピア
You are my utopia.
いつの日か この場所で出会えるなら
If someday we can meet in this place,
I MISS YOU I MISS YOU
I NEED YOU I NEED YOU
サクシ サクシ
Sexy, Sexy.
ねえ？ 部屋にこない？
Hey, won't you come to my room?
ナイショの話
I'll let you in on
聞かせてあげる
a little secret.
今宵ノレないなら
If you can't get into the groove tonight,
TAKE AWAYしても
even if you take me away,
どうしようもないね
there's just nothing we can do.
ふらちな夜に心も濡れた 時はもどせない
My heart got drenched in a naughty night, time can't be undone.
COME BACK COME BACK
COME BACK
情熱の かなたから蜃気楼
A mirage of passion from afar,
揺らして 揺らして 揺らして 揺らして
shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it,
気持ちいいこと パラダイス
a feel-good paradise!
燃えさかる あの場所で出会えるなら
If we can meet in that burning place,
揺らして 揺らして 揺らして 揺らして
shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it!
Sexy Sexy Dance
星は青ざめ 花は乱れる
Stars turn pale, flowers scatter wildly,
ヤミのなかから キラキラと映してるの
shining glitteringly from within the darkness.
からみつく 指先の蜃気楼
A mirage wrapping around our fingertips,
じらして じらして じらして じらして
tease me, tease me, tease me, tease me,
ジリジリいかせて
drive me wild and impatient!
いつまでも このあたりで恋してる
I'll be in love around here forever.
I MISS YOU I MISS YOU
I NEED YOU I NEED YOU
Sexy Sexy You
BABY BABY BABY BABY
あなた ユートピア
you are my utopia.
情熱の かなたには蜃気楼
A passionate mirage in the distance,
揺らして 揺らして 揺らして 揺らして
shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it,
何度も揺らして...
shake it over and over...
キラキラと Sexy Sexy
shining glitteringly, Sexy Sexy!
Are my eyes deceiving me?
Your soul starts to fade
Unleash your magic to me
Now it's time not to worry
Do believe in me
A journey we have to see
Rurira rari ra
Incomplete melody
Sung with a sweet but yet a sad symphony
Unwavering spirit that you told me
How can I do it when you're not even here
Oh, let me
Let out the words I could say to you right now,
I can only tell you a bit
Overwhelm me with your kindness is a gift
that I could never ever trade with anything
Let the time send this song to your ears
I hope one day you will sing it to me
Versatile melody that I tried to write
Every day I would pray in my heart, 'cause I'm reaching the sky
In a time full of worries, no light I could see
Do you want me to be here?
Nulling all the emotions you're supposed to feel
Even voice I wanna hear
Shalala Shalila
Incomplete melody, arriving in your ears like it's destiny
Rurira rarira, incomplete memory
Showing all the warmth that I have ever feel
呼んで
Yonde
Sing out
夜の記憶
Yoru no kioku
Shout out
火は燃える
Hi wa moeru
星屑のカケラたちは今願いになる
Hoshikuzu no kakera tachi wa ima negai ni naru
新たな喜びを願うの
Arata na yorokobi wo negau no
Rurira Rarira
A complete melody, has been sung in the world so far you can't see
Let the wind, let the sea carry this melody
Legacy, timeless song that carry all the wish
I believe
All the words I could say right now
I can only tell you a little bit
Overwhelm me with your kindness is a gift that I could never ever trade with anything
Let the time send this song to you
I hope one day you will sing it to me
Versatile melody that I tried to write
Every day I will sing it aloud, and I will try to shine
この声を聴いて
Kono koe wo kiite
Terima kasih untuk semua perhatian yang telah kuterima
As gentle breeze passed through your soul this time
I believe, everything will be fine
Every day I would sing it aloud, this is my time to shine
はい、ということで、えっと、マリンちゃんとリスちゃんと、え、歌った歌を二曲続けて聴いてもらいました。
So, we just listened to two songs in a row sung with Marine and Risu!
いや、どうだったみんな？
How was it, everyone?
マリンちゃんはね、あの、セクシーセクシーっていう歌をね、あの、ころねが大好きな歌なんだけど、マリンと合うかなと思って歌って
Marine's song, you know, 'Sexy Sexy', is a song Korone loves so much, so I thought it would fit Marine and sang it.
リスちゃんのオリジナル曲をね、ずっと歌いたかったの。今回ちょっとね、あの、多分初挑戦めちゃめちゃだったと思うけど
I've always wanted to sing Risu's original song. This time, it was probably my first try and super messy, but...
あの、頑張ってね、あの、覚えて、あの、一緒に歌いたいなと思って今回歌えてね、すごい嬉しかった。
I worked hard to memorize it because I wanted to sing it together, so I'm really happy we could sing it this time.
二人ともありがとう！
Thank you both so much!
いや、楽しかったね。楽しかったって言ってもね、まだ続くんですけどね。
Man, that was fun. Though I say it was fun, it's still going!
コーさん？
Koh-san?
コーさん？どうしようかゆっで
Koh-san? What should we do, Kayu—
あ、お返ししてくれました！コーさん4周年おめでとう！
Ah, you gave it back! Happy 4th anniversary, Korone!
ありがとう、かゆ！あ、かゆもさ、あのコン月ノ... 今月の6日だっけ？
Thank you, Kayu! Oh, Kayu, wasn't your 4th anniversary on the 6th of this month?
6日に、4周年だったからそうそうそう！
On the 6th, it was my 4th anniversary, so yeah, yeah!
二人でね、迎えました！
We celebrated it together!
見えてる？
"Can you see us?"
おかころでよ、おかころで、おかころと言えばいつもね
"Speaking of Okakoro, it's always..."
狂ったMCが定番なんですけど、ね？
"...that crazy MC style that's standard, right?"
狂った…あ、そうそうね。え、今回もじゃあなんか
"Crazy... Ah, right, right. Um, this time too, like..."
皆さん思い出ある？おかころでさ、やったことでさ
"Do you all have memories? Of things we did as Okakoro..."
やっぱね、二人でバイクに乗ってるコントみたいなやつが、やっぱ思い出深いのかな？
"After all, that skit where the two of us ride a motorcycle, I guess that brings back strong memories?"
やっとく？え、知らない人もいるから
"Should we do it? Well, since there are people who don't know it..."
一回バイクってみた。そうだい、今大勢の人が見てくれてるから
"...try riding a motorcycle. That's right, since a huge crowd is watching right now..."
そうだよね、なんか初めて見るよって人、そうそういるから。え、ちょっと待って、迎えに来るわ
"That's right, there are people seeing us for the first time. Wait, I'll go pick you up."
わかった。じゃあここらへんで…わかった。じゃあここらへんで
"Got it. Then around here... Got it. Then around here."
ころさんまだかな？
"Is Korone-san still not here?"
あ、来た来た！待て乗ってないから走ってきて！
"Ah, she's here! Wait, you're not riding, run over here!"
あ、おかゆ迎えに来たよ。あ、ありがと、ありがと
"Ah, Okayu came to pick me up. Ah, thanks, thanks."
よっこいしょ。いいかい？捕まえてな。こうしに捕まってるんだよ
"Heave-ho. Ready? Hold on tight. Hold on around the waist, okay?"
なんでおかゆの方が離れてるんだよ！あれはなんかあの、自転車みたいになってるから、あのみんなで乗るやつ
"Why are you even further away, Okayu?! That's like, a bicycle thing where everyone rides together..."
え、待って、ころさんのさ、なんか可愛いのある！あのさ、ここさ、ステージさ、作ったんだよ、すごくない？
"Wait, Korone, you have a cute one! We made this stage, isn't that amazing?"
すごい、可愛い！
"So cute!"
これ、新神ころやん！え、なんで一人なの？一緒に撮ろうよ！
"This is Inugami Koron-yan! Eh, why are you alone? Let's take it together!"
はーい！じゃあ…ピース！あ、違う！一緒に撮ろうよ！
"Okay! Then... Peace! Ah, no! Let's take it together!"
そう、ステージを今回ね、新しくあの運営さんに作ってもらって、なんかちょっとゲームっぽいような、ゲームが好きだから…
"Right, this time management made us a new stage, and it looks kind of like a game, since we love games..."
すごーい！ごめん、おかゆが作ってくれたの、ベロ犬はいなんだけど！
"So amazing! Sorry, the Doberman you made isn't here!"
なんでベロ犬いないの？！ちがう、ちょっとね、あの…あの…二軍だね、あのこは！なんでよ！違うの！次、次機械が合ったら作るから！
"Why is the Doberman not here?! No, wait, um... that kid is in the second string! Why?! No! Next time we have a chance, we'll make it!"
本当に？ころの中にはいるよ、ベロ犬が。ころの中に…ちょっとやじゃない？
"Really? In Korone's heart, the Doberman is there. In Korone's heart... Isn't that a bit creepy?"
なんで？あ、確かに、確かにやかも。じゃあ捨てとくね。なんでだよ！つらい！ええ！？
"Why? Ah, true, it might be creepy. Well, I'll throw it away then. Why?! That's harsh! Huh?!"
え、おかゆがベロ犬になってくれたらいいから。ベロ猫っていうことで。ベロベロ…あ、ちょっと嬉しい！
"Well, it'd be fine if Okayu became the Doberman. As a Dober-cat. Lick-lick... Ah, I'm kind of happy!"
え、こんなんでいいのかな？いいんじゃない？
"Eh, is this okay? Isn't it fine?"
いや、ころさん忘れてるじゃん！え、今日は2人で歌を歌おうって話だったじゃん！
"Hey, Korone-san, you forgot! Eh, today we talked about singing a song together, right?"
あ、確かに！そうだよ、歌を歌おうよ！
"Ah, that's right! That's right, let's sing a song!"
歌を歌おうよ！いや、でもなんか全部飛んじゃった！
"Let's sing a song! Well, but it all flew out of my head!"
いや、あのね、おかゆと今回ね、あの、おかゆを誘いたくって、で、あの、歌いたい曲があったんよ。だから今回その歌をね、おかゆと一緒に歌ってくれないかなって言って
"Well, you see, this time I wanted to invite Okayu, and, well, there was a song I wanted to sing. So I asked if Okayu would sing it with me this time."
で、あの、おかゆはね、「え、いいよ、ころさんのためなら、僕はいとこにでも行くよ」みたいなこと言ってくれて…ちょっと持ってるね！ちょっと持ったけど！
"And, well, Okayu said, 'Eh, sure, for Korone's sake, I'll go anywhere' or something... You're exaggerating a bit! I exaggerated a bit, but!"
あ、今回はね、でもおかゆは「いいよ」って、あの、言ってくれてね、今回はその、その曲を一緒に…うん、歌いたいと思います！
"Ah, this time, well, Okayu said 'Sure' and, um, told me that, so this time, um, together with that song... yeah, I'd like to sing it!"
はい！オッケーです！
"Yes! Okay!"
いいですか？オッケーです！みんなじゃあここスクショして、可愛いから！
"Is that okay? It's okay! Everyone take a screenshot here, because it's cute!"
ドングリ！ドングリ！マツボックリ！マツボックリ！イェーイ！
"Acorn! Acorn! Pinecone! Pinecone! Yay!"
よし！じゃあ、歌いますか！
"Alright! Then, shall we sing?"
歌いましょう！
"Let's sing!"
はい！というわけででは、聞いてください。「カラフル」！
"Yes! So with that, please listen. 'Colorful'!"
いつもの黒だった瞳の奥の景色捨てたら夢見つけた
When I abandoned the scenery deep in my eyes,
which were always black, I found a dream.
何もない世界で作る絆は強い意志を与えた
The bonds we forge in an empty world
gave us a strong will.
裏返した日常でまた
In our inverted everyday life once again,
走って行く先に君はいた
you were waiting at the end where I ran.
触れた心は輝いた鮮やかな色になって羽ばたくよ希望を乗せて
Our touched hearts shone into vibrant colors,
taking flight carrying hope!
無限に広がる空の下集まった
Gathered beneath the infinitely spreading sky,
願い守り進めば
if we keep going, protecting our wishes—
まだ誰も知らない
toward a tomorrow that
明日へと
nobody knows yet...
引き寄せられるように覗いた瞬間
The moment I peeked as if drawn in,
光の糸は秘密結んだ
the threads of light tied a secret.
細くちぎれそうなからまった運命
A fragile, tangled fate like it's about to tear—
きっとまだ変われる
I'm sure we can still change.
間違えても信じた道は
Even if we took a wrong turn, the path we believed in
新しい景色を照らすだろう
will illuminate a new scenery.
巡る時の中笑って様々な想い持って
Laughing amidst the revolving time, holding various feelings,
始めようまた一から
let's start all over again from one.
たどり着いた儚い奇跡壊れないように
So that this transient miracle we reached won't break,
手を伸ばし繋げば
if we reach out and connect our hands,
ほら日々は側でいつまでも
look, our days are by our side, forever and ever.
まだ透明な私たちはどんな色にでも
Because we, still transparent, can be dyed
染まることが出来るから夢叶えよう
in any color, let's make our dreams come true.
走って行く先々に君はいた
You were there at the places we ran to.
触れた
Touched,
心は輝いた鮮やかな色になって
our hearts shone and became vivid colors,
羽ばたくよ希望を乗せて
taking flight carrying hope.
無限に広がる空の下集まった
Gathered beneath the infinitely spreading sky,
願い守り進めば
if we keep going, protecting our wishes—
君と誓ったあの日の記憶
the memories of that day we swore to each other
今超えて過去から
now transcending from the past,
まだ誰も知らない明日へと
toward a tomorrow that nobody knows yet...
はぁ、カラフルえもかったよね！
Haah, "Colorful" was so emotional, right?
おかゆありがとう！
Okayu, thank you!
はい、ではでは毎年恒例のこちら出ます！
Yes, well then, here comes our annual tradition!
じゃーん！
Ta-da!
はい！
Yes!
え、おろにゃーん！？
Eh, Oronyan?!
こんばんはにゃん！ネコ妖怪、ジバにゃんにゃん！
Good evening nyan! Cat Yo-kai, Jibanyan nyan!
え？ころねちゃんが4周年ライブをやれるって聞いて駆け付けてきたにゃんよ！
Eh? I heard Korone-chan is holding her 4th anniversary live and came rushing over nyan!
デビュー4周年本当に おめでとうにゃん！
Huge congratulations on your 4th anniversary nyan!
ライブにめっちゃ盛り上がってるにゃんね！
You're getting super hyped up for the live nyan!
おれっちもついつい踊り出しくなっちゃうにゃん！
It makes even me want to start dancing nyan!
そういえば、おれっちの目覚まし時計を使ってくれてたりくれてなかったりって聞いたにゃん！
Come to think of it, I heard you were or weren't using my alarm clock nyan!
ありがとうにゃんね！ちゃんと起きられてたにゃんか？
Thanks nyan! Were you waking up properly nyan?
とっても長い時間配信やってるみたいだから、ちゃんと眠れてるか心配にゃん！
It looks like you stream for very long hours, so I'm worried if you're sleeping properly nyan!
たまにはチョコボー食べてゴロゴロするといいにゃん！
You should eat Chocobor and relax sometimes nyan!
じゃあころねちゃん、これからも頑張ってくれにゃん！
Well Korone-chan, keep doing your best from now on nyan!
おれっちも応援してるにゃん！
I'm rooting for you too nyan!
バイバイにゃん！指々ーにゃん！
Bye-bye nyan! Yubi-yubi nyan!
え、ちょっと待って！
Eh, wait a second!
え、待って？本当に知らなかったんだけど！
Eh, wait? I really didn't know at all!
え、待ってジバにゃん！？
Eh, wait, Jibanyan?!
えーーー！
Ehhhh!
ジバにゃーーん！ありがとう！
Jibanyaaan! Thank you!
目覚まし時計はちょっと壊れちゃったけど
My alarm clock broke a little bit, but
えー嬉しい！
Eh, I'm so happy!
あの、え、ジバにゃんの目覚まし時計を使っててですね、あの、使いすぎて壊れまして、
Um, uh, I was using Jibanyan's alarm clock, and, you know, I used it too much and it broke, and
あの、早く！早く！早く！
um, hurry! hurry! hurry!
みたいになったんですけど、
I wanted to become...
それがね、え、あ、すごい、なんか、え、
but you know, um, wow, like, um,
しぼにゃん、ありがとね、しぼにゃん！
Shibonyan, thank you, Shibonyan!
え、待って、グッズ、グッズを出すテンションでいたのに、
Wait, I was supposed to be announcing merchandise with all that hype,
あの、江戸城、え、これグッズ？
but like, Edo Castle? Eh, is this merchandise?
あ、紹介…
Ah, introduction...
え、あ、しぼにゃん、ありがとね！うれしー！ということで、あの、グッズも出ます。せーの、
Oh, Shibonyan, thank you! I'm so happy! So, the merchandise is also coming out. Ready,
どーん！
ta-da!
やだ、こんなテンションで、はい！犬神ころね
No way, with this kind of hype, yes! Inugami Korone's
活動4周年記念グッズ、出ます！
4th Anniversary Commemorative Goods are releasing!
紹介したほうがいいですよね。
I should probably introduce them, right?
はい、あ、こちらですね、えっと、まず初めに、
Yes, so first of all,
ラバーマット、こちらは、え、Hikoson先生描き下ろしの、
this rubber mat, illustrated by Hikoson-sensei,
え、デザインとなっておりまして、これは、のどかなね、あの、村、村っていうのかな、村を、え、毛玉ころねをお散歩させてる光景みたいな感じの、ラバーマットになっておりますので、
features a cozy, idyllic village where Kedama Korone is taking a stroll—sort of like that kind of rubber mat.
あの、すごい、あの、ほのぼのした気持ちになれたらと思います。かわいい！これめちゃかわいい。
So I hope it makes you feel really cozy and warm. Cute! This is super cute.
え、次、
Next,
毛玉ころねのぬいぐるみ、これマジでめっちゃかわいいからね、これ！
the Kedama Korone plushie! This is seriously, super cute, guys, this!
え、これはね、あの、お洋服も脱げるようになってて、
And this one actually lets you take off its clothes,
なんで脱げるようになってんねん、って話でしょ。え、まだ第二弾が出るんですか、みたいな。それはわかんないけどね。
and you're probably like, "Why can you take them off?!" Who knows, maybe there'll be a second volume?
でも、なんか脱げるようになっているんで、なんか着替えとかも、なんかね、ま、これできるならしたいな、みたいな感じのぬいぐるみとなっております。
Anyway, since it's designed to be removable, I'd love it if we could do outfit changes and stuff in the future, so that's the kind of plushie it is.
はい、で、次、
Alright, next,
毛玉ころねのジャージ！
the Kedama Korone Jersey!
これは、毛玉ころねなんだけど、これはねころねがね、あの、書きました。
This is Kedama Korone, but Korone herself drew this design.
えーっとね、骨のデザイン、なんかあの、男の子も女の子も、なんか老若男女問わず、こう、なんか、
Umm, the bone design—regardless of whether you're a guy or a girl, young or old—
着て、かっこよく着こなせるような、かっこいいデザインにしてみました。
we tried to make it a cool design that anyone can wear and pull off stylishly.
で、あの胸元にね、あのバッククロージャーっぽいようなハート型も書いてあって、
And right on the chest, there's a heart shape that looks a bit like a bag closure.
え、ちょっとすごいね、ころねちょっと結構頑張ってデザインしたので、これよかったらね、あの、みんなに着て欲しいなと思います。
Korone worked really hard on this design, so if you like it, I really hope you all will get one and wear it!
で、サイズはXLで統一になっちゃうんですが、よかったらぜひぜひ、あの、
And for the size, it's unified as XL, but if you'd like, please, please...
着てね！
wear it!
はい！
Yes!
で、フルセット、こちらフルセット買っていただいた方には、
And for the full set, those who purchase the full set
ころねが描き下ろした、このね、あのステッカーなんですけど、あの名前がね、こうピュピュピュピュって書けるようになってるんで、
will get this sticker drawn by Korone where you can write names like "pyu-pyu-pyu-pyu!"
これね、あの新学期始まったりしたらね、これをノートとかね、カバンとかに貼ってたら「何それ？」みたいな、人気者になれること間違いなしなので、
If you stick this on your notebook or bag when the new school term starts, people will be like, "What's that?!" So it's guaranteed to make you popular.
ぜひぜひ、あの、買ってください！
So please, please make sure to buy it!
はい、というわけで、えっと、あのね、けだま、え、けだまころねっていうのはね、砂漠先生っていう方が生み出してくださったんですけど、本当に砂漠先生ありがとうございます！
So, um, Kedama Korone was brought to life by Sabaku-sensei, so huge thanks to Sabaku-sensei!
はい！
Yes!
今回はね、あのけだま、ころねのね、あの、いっぱい、いっぱい、あのグッズを作ったので、ぜひ、あの、見て見てね。あのこのあと10時から発売です。よろしくね！
This time we've made lots and lots of Kedama Korone goods, so please go check them out. They go on sale starting at 10 PM today. Thank you!
はい、で、これで終わらない。えっと、最後にもう1曲みんなに聞いてほしい歌があるので、その歌を歌ってバイバイしようと思います。では聞いてください。
And this isn't the end! Lastly, there's one more song I want everyone to hear, so we'll say our goodbyes after singing that song. Please give it a listen.
いかにも蛸にも お腹 Goo Goo
Like an octopus or a snail, my tummy goes goo-goo
手に持つ少なめ いざ Zun Zun
Carrying light luggage, now it's time to zun-zun
飯は食わねば 寝る寝る Never Na タイムスリップーya
If you don't eat, you gotta sleep, never na—Time slip-py-ya!
ここどこ迷子で GO GO GO
Where am I, a lost child, go go go!
Dancing ダーウィン じゃんじゃん進化進行
Dancing Darwin, rapid-fire evolution in progress!
干渉あり 人類発祥どうこう
Meddling allowed, human origins and all that
ア良い感じ そろそろ出発進行
Ah, feels nice, departure in progress soon
去る者追う猿ぱぴぱぴぷ〜
Chasing away those who leave, pypi-pipi-poo~
(ぷちょへんざ ぷちょぷちょへんざ)
(Put your hands up, put-put your hands up)
欲しいモンはホラ 孤高これぞ旦那
What I want is look, the master himself
さぁわんわん わんわんわんわん わんっ チキチキワッハー！
Bow-wow, wow-wow-wow-wow, woof! Chikichiki Wah-ha!
脳内全開 Yeah えっやっぱっぴParty
Mind wide open, yeah, yappa-ppa party
笑って泣いて 踊れば あいあいあっおー
Laugh and cry, and if you dance, ai-ai-ah-oh
パンドラ開け ドヴァァって飲まれたRaw ごらん遊ばせ
Open Pandora's box, gulping it down raw, behold!
あちゃちゃちゃちゃちゃちゃぱりーん おーわっあっ あいあい
Achatacha-chatacha-chapparin, o-wa-ah, ai-ai
気分はHigh とんとんだん おーわっあっ あいあい 愛の間合い どんどんぱん
Feeling is high, tonton-dan, o-wa-ah, ai-ai, timing of love, dondon-pan
つながってんだ 記録なんだ ちなみに連綿つむいだ
We're connected, it's a record, spinning threads through generations
犬猿人 GO! 報酬いいんだ
Dog, ape, human, go! The reward is good
働いてんだ 歴なんだ 休みなし毎日が
Working hard, it's a history, every day without a break
月月金土 あーん 乱心
Monday, Tuesday, Friday, Saturday—ah, derangement
乱心ダーウィン じゃんじゃんドタ進行
Deranged Darwin, rapid-fire rush in progress
人類抹消 あるでしょ AI暴走
Human extinction, could it be AI going rogue?
アもう最深部 そろそろ計画進行
Ah, the deepest part, project schedule in progress soon
もうゆびゆびまで ワン・ツー・スリー ライオライオ だんだんしゃあ
Right down to your fingertips, one, two, three! Roar, roar, gradually sliding down
オーマイガ オーマイワイフ
Oh my god, oh my wife,
ようやく真理辿り着いた
I've finally reached the ultimate truth.
無限 螺旋 抜け 無心で
Breaking out of the infinite spiral mindlessly,
ほらウェーイ ほらウェーイ
Hey, way! Hey, way!
（ぷちょへんざっ ぷちょぷちょへんざっ）
(Put your hands up, put your, put your hands up)
欲しいモンは ホラ これだ旦那
What you want, look, here it is, boss.
さあわんわん わんわんわんっ ワンッ
Now, woof woof, woof woof woof! Woof!
チキチキワッパー！
Chiki Chiki Whopper!
脳内全開Yeah やっぱっぱPa
Mind wide open, yeah, as expected, pa!
笑って泣いて 踊れば あいいああっー
If you laugh, cry, and dance, aii-aa-ah!
パンドラ開いて ドヴァッて飲まれたRaw
Opening Pandora's box, swallowed up raw,
ごらん遊ばせ あちゃちゃいちゃいちゃいちゃっパリーン♪
Behold, a-cha-cha-i-cha-i-cha-i-cha-parīn♪
おーわっあっ アイアイ 気分はHigh
O-wa-ah, ai-ai, feeling high,
とんとんたん
ton-ton-tan,
おーわっあっ アイアイ 愛の間合い どどんどぱん
o-wa-ah, ai-ai, in the space of love, don-don-pan
ぷちょへんざっ
Put your hands up
はい、今のわ、え、オリジナル曲なんですけど、
Yeah, that was, um, my original song, but,
え、この後ですね、すぐにMVも公開するので、
um, right after this, the MV will also be released,
ぜひぜひそちらもリスナーさんみんなに楽しんで欲しいなと思います。
so I really hope all the listeners will enjoy that too.
めっちゃね、かわいくてかっこよく仕上がってるからね、ぜひみんな見てください。
It's turned out super cute and cool, so everyone please go check it out.
で、みんなに今日は、え、渡すものがあります。
And today, I have something to give to everyone.
いつもはね、帰ってこないあれを今日はね、返すんだよ。ちょっと待っててね。
The thing that normally doesn't come back, I'm going to return it today. Just wait a second, okay?
あ、新鮮だ。新鮮な指だよ。
Ah, it's fresh. Fresh fingers.
ほら、さっき取っちゃってごめんね。
Look, sorry for taking them earlier.
はい、みんなどうぞ。
Here you go, everyone.
なんであるの？
Why aren't you taking them?
なんである？みんなもでしょ？はい。
Why? You guys too, right? Here.
え、なんで？
Eh, why?
え、なんで？なんで？ほら、ほら、素敵。おいし…おいしゅ、おいしゅじゃない。
Eh, why? Why? Look, look, wonderful. Delicious—delicious, no, not delicious.
はい、はい、返すよ。はい、はい、はい、はい、はい、はい、はい、はい、はい、はい。
Here, here, I'm returning them. Here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here.